<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>AWS Feed</title><link>http://www.foo.bar/test.xml</link><description>AWS Stuff</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 08:18:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated Fargate task launch failures</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 7:31 AM PST on December 7 and 2:20 AM PST on December 8, ECS experienced increased API error rates, latencies, and task launch failures. API error rates and latencies recovered by 6:10 PM PST on December 7. After this point, ECS customers using the EC2 launch type were fully recovered. ECS customers using the Fargate launch type along with EKS customers using Fargate continued to see decreasing impact in the form of insufficient capacity errors between 4:40 PM PST on December 7 and 2:20 AM on December 8. The service is now operating normally. A small set of customers may still experience low levels of insufficient capacity errors and will be notified using the Personal Health Dashboard in that case. There was no impact to running tasks during the event although any ECS task that failed health checks would have been stopped because of that failing health check.
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;

We'd like to share more information about the service event on Tuesday December 7th. Additional details are available below. Should you have any questions, please contact AWS Support. &amp;lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/message/12721/"&amp;gt;https://aws.amazon.com/message/12721/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 02:29:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated Fargate task launch failures</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>ECS has recovered from the issue earlier in the day. Task launches using the EC2 launch type are fully recovered. Fargate task launches are currently experiencing increased insufficient capacity errors. We are working on addressing this and have recently seen a decrease in these errors while continuing to work towards full recovery. In the interim, tasks sizes smaller than 4vCPU are less likely to see insufficient capacity errors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 23:01:37 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated Fargate task launch failures</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>ECS has recovered from the issue earlier in the day. Task launches using the EC2 launch type are fully recovered. Fargate task launches are currently experiencing increased insufficient capacity errors. We are working on addressing this. In the interim, tasks sizes smaller than 4vCPU are less likely to see insufficient capacity errors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 19:30:07 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated Fargate task launch failures</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>ECS has recovered from the issue earlier in the day. Task launches using the EC2 launch type are fully recovered. We have identified the root cause for the increased Fargate launch failures and are starting to see recovery. As we work towards full recovery, customers may experience insufficient capacity errors and these are being addressed as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 17:31:42 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated Fargate task launch failures</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>ECS has recovered from the issue earlier in the day. Task launches using the EC2 launch type are fully recovered. We have identified the root cause for the increased Fargate launch failures and are working towards recovery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 16:44:27 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated Fargate task launch failures</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>ECS has recovered from the issue earlier in the day, but we are still investigating task launch failures using the Fargate launch type. Task launches using the EC2 launch type are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 15:32:57 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 3:40 AM and 6:45 AM PDT we experienced increased API error rates for ECS in the US-EAST-1 Region. In most cases, API calls succeeded when retried.  We continue to work to recover residual impact and have opened notifications for the remaining impacted customers via the Personal Health Dashboard.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 07:12:12 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased API error rates for ECS in the US-EAST-1 Region. We have identified the root cause and continue to work towards recovery. In most cases, a retry of the API operation will succeed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 06:15:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased API error rates for ECS in the US-EAST-1 Region. We have identified the issue and are working towards mitigation. In most cases, a retry of the API operation will succeed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 05:24:40 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased API error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 04:55:56 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Launches</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between November 25 5:15 AM and November 26 1:08 AM PST, we experienced elevated API and task launch error rates, delayed metrics impacting Capacity Provider scaling, CloudWatch Container Insights, and CloudWatch metrics for ECS. Running tasks were not impacted. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 01:17:52 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased API Error Rates and Launches</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>CloudWatch metrics for ECS and Capacity Providers have recovered. We expect to see recovery on slow task deprovisioning. which is causing tasks to remain in a deactivating or deprovisioning state for extended periods of time, once CloudMap is fully recovered. For ECS tasks using awsvpc networking mode, including Fargate tasks, this means the ENI associated with the task remains provisioned longer than normal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:29:41 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased API Error Rates and Launches</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>CloudWatch metrics for ECS and Capacity Providers have recovered. We continue working to resolve slow task deprovisioning which is causing tasks to remain in a deactivating or deprovisioning state for extended periods of time. For ECS tasks using awsvpc networking mode, including Fargate tasks, this means the ENI associated with the task remains provisioned longer than normal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:11:04 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased API Error Rates and Launches</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are starting to see recovery for CloudWatch metrics for ECS and Capacity Providers. CloudWatch Container Insights is now showing recent metrics from ECS. ECS continues working to resolve slow tasks deprovisioning which causes tasks to remain in a deactivating or deprovisioning states for extended periods of time. For ECS tasks using awsvpc networking mode, including Fargate tasks, this means the ENI associated with the task remains provisioned longer than normal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 22:49:57 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased API Error Rates and Launches</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>ECS is investigating slow deprovisioning of tasks causing tasks to remain in a deactivating or deprovisioning for extended periods of time. For ECS tasks using awsvpc networking mode, including Fargate tasks, this means the ENI associated with the task remains provisioned longer than normal. CloudWatch Container Insights is now correctly showing recent metrics from ECS. CloudWatch metrics for ECS and Capacity Providers are continuing to see impact while we wait for Kinesis and CloudWatch recovery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 21:06:03 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 2:40 PM and 4:45 PM PST, we experienced increased error rates for file system creation requests in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is now operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 17:02:14 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are continuing to experience increased error rates for file system creation requests in the US-EAST-1 Region, and are actively working to resolve the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:13:45 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates for file system creation requests in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:46:43 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 5:14 PM and 6:09 PM PDT, we experienced increased error rates for API requests in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is now operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 19:08:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 9:37 AM and 1:45 PM PST customers may have experienced increased latency for file operations and were unable to mount file systems using newly created mount targets in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 14:00:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Latencies for file operations in the US-EAST-1 Region are back to normal. Customers continue to be unable to mount using newly-created mount targets in US-EAST-1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 13:38:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased latencies for some file operations, and we can confirm customers are unable to create new endpoints for accessing file systems in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 11:43:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 6:08 PM and 11:12 PM PDT, we experienced increased provisioning latencies for Network Load Balancers in the US-EAST-1 Region, which has now fully recovered. We are continuing to experience delays in the propagation of CloudWatch metrics for load balancers. The system used to generate these metrics has begun to recover, and we anticipate full recovery in the next few hours after we process the backlog of metrics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 23:22:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm delayed propagation of load balancer CloudWatch metrics and provisioning latencies for Network Load Balancers in the US-EAST-1 Region, and are continuing to work towards resolution. Connectivity to existing load balancers is not affected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 22:08:41 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased provisioning latencies for new load balancers, delayed propagation of load balancer CloudWatch metrics, and inconsistent health check statuses from the DescribeTargetHealth API for Network Load Balancers in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:21:02 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] API Errors, Increased Provisioning Times / Registration Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Starting at 5:05 AM PDT, we experienced periods of increased error rates and provisioning/registration latencies for ELB APIs in the US-EAST-1 Region. The periods of elevated API error rates were resolved at 7:55 AM PDT. The periods of increased provisioning/latencies were resolved for the vast majority of customers by 8:31 AM PDT, with full recovery at 9:11 AM PDT. Connectivity to existing load balancers was not affected. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 10:38:20 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] API Errors, Increased Provisioning Times / Registration Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased API error rates and increased provisioning/registration latencies for ELBs in the US-EAST-1 Region. Connectivity to existing load balancers is not affected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 06:47:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Provisioning and Scaling Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Beginning at 11:13 AM PDT we experienced increased provisioning and scaling latencies for Elastic Load Balancers in the US-EAST-1 Region. Recovery for scaling latency occurred at 1:15 PM PDT, and recovery for provisioning latency occurred at 3:35 PM PDT. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 15:44:17 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Provisioning and Scaling Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>The team is closely monitoring the issue with EC2 APIs, and continues to see reductions in scaling and provisioning latencies. Other load balancing operations, including target registrations and traffic processing are unaffected. Once the issue with the EC2 APIs is resolved, we will process the backlog of any pending operations before we observe full resolution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 14:39:37 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Provisioning and Scaling Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have determined the root cause of increased scaling latencies for Elastic Load Balancers in the US-EAST-1 Region and are working towards mitigation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 13:38:33 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Provisioning and Scaling Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased provisioning and scaling latencies for Elastic Load Balancers in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 12:50:45 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Degraded instance registration</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 7:05 PM and 8:50 PM PDT, we experienced increased load balancer provisioning and back-end target registration times in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 21:27:11 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Connectivity Issues for Network Load Balancers</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Starting at 11:24 AM PST, some load balancers in the USE1-AZ2, USE1-AZ4, and USE1-AZ5 Availability Zones experienced connectivity issues when terminating TLS (SSL) connections in the US-EAST-1 Region. Engineers worked to identify the root cause of the event, ultimately deploying an update to recover USE1-AZ4 at 1:50 PM PST, USE1-AZ2 at 4:26 PM PST and USE1-AZ5 at 4:31 PM PST. Network Load Balancers not terminating TLS (SSL) connections were not affected by this event. Some PrivateLink endpoints were also affected by the issue. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 17:07:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Connectivity Issues for Network Load Balancers</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have completed the update in all affected Availability Zones and all Network Load Balancers are now operating normally. We are working through a backlog of Network Load Balancer created and back-end instance registrations, but at this stage all operations should be operating normally. We will continue to monitor recovery and post an update shortly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 16:38:52 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Connectivity Issues for Network Load Balancers</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have completed applying the fix in both the USE1-AZ4 and USE1-AZ2 Availability Zones. We have started the process of updating the final Availability Zone, USE1-AZ5. We expect to see full recovery within the next 30 minutes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 16:28:12 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Connectivity Issues for Network Load Balancers</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to make progress and are now seeing recovery for affected Network Load Balancers in the USE1-AZ2 Availability Zone. We will continue on the remainder of that Availability Zone before completing USE1-AZ5, the final Availability Zone. Again, for Network Load Balancers that have recovered, we do not expect further impact.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 16:03:39 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Connectivity Issues for Network Load Balancers</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have resolved the issue that affected our deployment of the fix to the final cell in the USE1-AZ4 Availability Zone, and continue to deploy to Availability Zones USE1-AZ2 and USE1-AZ5. We have taken steps to accelerate recovery but are also being cautious to not apply the fix to more than one Availability Zone at a time out of an abundance of caution. For customers that have seen their Network Load Balancer recover, we do not expect any further impact. For customers that are still waiting for recovery, we expect to see that in the coming hour or two as we work through the remaining Availability Zone. For immediate mitigation, customers can create a new Network Load Balancer in the unaffected Availability Zones and register the existing back-end targets with it. We’ll continue to provide updates as we progress through the remaining Availability Zones.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 15:27:47 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 1:29 PM and 7:34 PM PDT we experienced increased error rates for the RDS Management Console and API calls. The issue is resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 20:06:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified the issue causing increased error rates with RDS Console and API calls in the US-EAST-1 Region and are working towards recovery.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 19:07:19 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to see increased error rates with Console and API calls in the US-EAST-1 Region and are working towards recovery. Connectivity to currently running instances is not affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 16:39:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to investigate increased error rates with Console and API calls in the US-EAST-1 Region. Connectivity to currently running instances is not affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 15:34:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased API error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 14:32:43 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Connectivity Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Beginning at 5:40 AM PDT, some RDS single-AZ instances experienced connectivity issues within a single Availability Zone in the US-EAST-1 Region. By 11:55 AM, 1% of instances in the affected AZ were still experiencing connectivity issues. We continue to work to recover all affected instances and volumes and will be communicating to the remaining impacted customers via the Personal Health Dashboard. For customers who need immediate recovery, we recommend performing a &amp;lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/USER_PIT.html"&amp;gt;point in time&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/USER_RestoreFromSnapshot.html"&amp;gt;snapshot recovery&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; of your DB instance from the AWS Management Console or RDS APIs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 14:15:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Connectivity Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are starting to see recovery for connectivity issues impacting some single-AZ instances in a single Availability Zone in the US-EAST-1 Region. We continue to work towards recovery for all impacted instances.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 08:25:03 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Connectivity Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating connectivity issues affecting some single-AZ RDS instances in a single Availability Zone in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 07:16:07 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased API Latencies and Management Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 8:21 AM and 10:01 AM PDT, we experienced increased API latencies and increased error rates for the RDS Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 10:09:17 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased API Latencies and Management Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased API latencies and increased error rates for the RDS Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 09:51:19 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Network Connectivity</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 11:28 AM and 11:31 AM PDT some Multi-AZ and Single-AZ RDS instances experienced network connectivity issues in the US-EAST-1 Region. All affected Multi-AZ RDS instances failed over to a second Availability Zone, which restored connectivity. The remaining Single-AZ RDS instances have now restored connectivity. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 13:28:34 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Network Connectivity</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 11:28 AM and 11:31 AM PDT some Multi-AZ and Single-AZ RDS instances experienced network connectivity issues in the US-EAST-1 Region. All affected Multi-AZ RDS instances failed over to a second Availability Zone, which restored connectivity. The majority of the Single-AZ RDS instances have recovered and we continue to work on restoring connectivity to a small number of remaining Single-AZ RDS instances.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 13:02:34 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Connectivity Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Beginning at 2:52 PM PDT, we experienced connectivity issues affecting some database instances in a single Availability Zone in the US-EAST-1 Region. Multi-AZ database instances functioned correctly and remained available. Connectivity was restored at 3:22 PM PDT, at which point the vast majority of database instances recovered. A small number of Single-AZ database instances remain unavailable and we are continuing to work to recover all affected database instances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 17:42:56 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Connectivity Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Beginning at 2:52 PM PDT, we experienced connectivity issues affecting some database instances in a single Availability Zone in the US-EAST-1 Region. Multi-AZ database instances functioned correctly and remain available. A small number of Single-AZ database instances remain unavailable and we are working to resolve the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 16:12:31 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Connectivity Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating connectivity issues affecting some database instances in a single Availability Zone in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 15:58:40 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased DNS Edit Propagation Time</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 4:08 PM and 4:58 PM PDT we experienced increased propagation times of DNS edits. Queries to existing DNS records were not affected by this issue. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 17:05:50 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased DNS Edit Propagation Time</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified the issue that has caused increased propagation times of DNS edits, and are working towards recovery. Queries to existing DNS records are not affected by this issue and are being answered normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 16:50:17 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased DNS Edit Propagation Time</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased propagation times of DNS edits to Route 53 DNS servers. Queries to existing DNS records are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 16:32:02 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Route 53 Console Errors</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 10:29 AM and 10:37 AM PDT customers experienced an elevated error rate when accessing the Route 53 Console. The issue has been resolved and all console requests are being answered normally. There was no impact to the Route 53 API, DNS, or Health Checking services, which were all operating normally during this time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 11:11:19 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Route 53 Console Errors</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have confirmed an issue with the Route 53 console which is causing an increased error rate. All calls to the Route 53 API and DNS servers are being answered normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 10:52:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Route 53 DNS Change Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 12:07 PM and 5:15 PM PST, customers experienced delays propagating changes submitted to the Route 53 API, as well as increased API error rates from 1:55 PM until 3:20 PM. This also affected provisioning of new resources that rely on Route 53 DNS, such as EFS, PrivateLink, Amazon MQ, Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka, API Gateway, DocumentDB, FSx for Lustre, Certificate Manager, Transfer for SFTP, EKS, CloudFormation, Chime Voice Connector, Global Accelerator, RDS, SageMaker Ground Truth, Amazon Managed Blockchain, Directory Service and Elastic Inference. The Route 53 API is now operating normally, and all changes that were accepted by the Route 53 API have been propagated. Queries for all existing records were answered normally during this time.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 17:21:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Route 53 DNS Change Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified root cause resulting in increased propagation times of DNS edits to the Route 53 DNS servers, and are working towards recovery. The Route 53 API is now accepting changes again, though these changes are still experiencing delays propagating as there is a significant backlog of changes to process. Queries to existing DNS records are not affected by this issue. This will also affect provisioning of new resources that rely on Route 53 for DNS, such as: EFS, PrivateLink, Amazon MQ, Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka, API Gateway, DocumentDB, FSx for Lustre, Certificate Manager, Transfer for SFTP, EKS, CloudFormation, Chime Voice Connector, Global Accelerator, RDS, SageMaker Ground Truth, Amazon Managed Blockchain and Directory Service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 15:45:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Route 53 DNS Change Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified root cause resulting in increased propagation times of DNS edits to the Route 53 DNS servers. The Route 53 API is temporarily not accepting MakeChange or CreateHostedZone requests in order to help accelerate recovery. Queries to existing DNS records are not affected by this issue. This will also affect provisioning of new resources that rely on Route 53 for DNS, such as: EFS, PrivateLink, Amazon MQ, Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka, API Gateway, DocumentDB, FSx for Lustre, Certificate Manager, Transfer for SFTP, EKS, CloudFormation, Chime Voice Connector and Global Accelerator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 15:08:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Route 53 DNS Change Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are still investigating increased propagation times of DNS edits to the Route 53 DNS servers. To help accelerate recovery, the Route 53 API is temporarily not accepting MakeChange or CreateHostedZone requests. Queries to existing DNS records are not affected by this issue. This will also affect provisioning of new resources that rely on Route 53 for DNS, such as: EFS, PrivateLink, Amazon MQ, Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka, API Gateway, DocumentDB, FSx for Lustre, Certificate Manager, Transfer for SFTP, EKS, CloudFormation and Chime Voice Connector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 14:58:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Route 53 DNS Change Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are still investigating increased propagation times of DNS edits to the Route 53 DNS servers. To help accelerate recovery, the Route 53 API is temporarily not accepting MakeChange or CreateHostedZone requests. This will also affect provisioning of new resources that rely on Route 53 for DNS, such as: EFS, PrivateLink, Amazon MQ, Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka, API Gateway.  Queries to existing DNS records are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 13:38:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Route 53 DNS Change Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are still investigating increased propagation times of DNS edits to the Route 53 DNS servers. This will affect provisioning of new resources that rely on Route 53 for DNS, such as EFS and PrivateLink. Queries to existing DNS records are not affected by this issue</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 13:21:15 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Route 53 DNS Change Issues</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased propagation times of DNS edits to the Route 53 DNS servers. Queries to existing DNS records are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 12:50:55 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Further information regarding DNS resolution</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>On October 22, 2019, we detected and then mitigated a DDoS (Distributed Denial of Service) attack against Route 53. Due to the way that DNS queries are processed, this attack was first experienced by many other DNS server operators as the queries made their way through DNS resolvers on the internet to Route 53. The attack targeted specific DNS names and paths, notably those used to access the global names for S3 buckets.

Because this attack was widely distributed, a small number of ISPs operating affected DNS resolvers implemented mitigation strategies of their own in an attempt to control the traffic. This is causing DNS lookups through these resolvers for a small number of AWS names to fail. We are doing our best to identify and contact these operators, as quickly as possible, and working with them to enhance their mitigations so that they do not cause impact to valid requests. If you are experiencing issues, please contact us so we can work with your operator to help resolve.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 17:44:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased API error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 9:25 AM and 11:30 AM PDT, we experienced increased errors when making changes to some hosted zones, and creating new hosted zones using the Route 53 API and Console. The issue has been recovered, and all services are operating normally. DNS queries were not affected by this issue, which were all answered normally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 11:33:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased API error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified root cause and are working towards recovery of elevated error rates using the Route 53 API. DNS queries are not affected by this issue, which are all being answered normally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 11:26:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Email Receiving Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 12:25 PM and 1:52 PM PDT we experienced elevated delivery delays in the US-EAST-1 Region for mail sent to a specific external email provider. This issue impacted the SendEmail/SendRawEmail APIs as well as calls made to the SMTP endpoint. All delayed emails have now been delivered. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 14:20:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Email Receiving Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are currently investigating elevated latencies in our email-sending APIs in the US-EAST-1 Region. This includes the SendEmail/SendRawEmail APIs as well as calls made to the SMTP endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 13:46:48 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 9:37 AM PST and 3:18 PM PST we experienced elevated error rates for our email-sending and email-receiving APIs in the US-EAST-1 Region. This included the SendEmail/SendRawEmail APIs as well as calls made to the sending and receiving SMTP endpoints. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 16:33:38 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are seeing recovery for our email-sending and email-receiving APIs in the US-EAST-1 Region. This includes the SendEmail/SendRawEmail APIs as well as calls made to the sending and receiving SMTP endpoints. We will continue to monitor this issue until fully recovered in US-EAST-1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 13:54:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm elevated error rates for our email-sending APIs in the US-EAST-1 Region. This includes the SendEmail/SendRawEmail APIs as well as calls made to the SMTP endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 11:43:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated email-sending API error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 4:31 AM and 6:10 AM PDT we experienced elevated error rates for our email-sending SMTP endpoint in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 06:42:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated email-sending API error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified the root cause of the issue causing elevated error rates for our email-sending SMTP endpoint in the US-EAST-1 Region and we are currently working to resolve.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 06:06:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated email-sending API error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are currently investigating elevated error rates for our email-sending APIs in the US-EAST-1 Region. This includes the calls made to the SMTP endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 05:18:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 5:25 AM PDT and 7:20 AM PDT we experienced elevated latencies in our email-sending and email-receiving APIs in the US-EAST-1 Region. This included the SendEmail/SendRawEmail APIs as well as calls made to the sending and receiving SMTP endpoints. Messages successfully submitted to SES during that time are being delivered and processed with a delay. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 07:48:51 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are currently investigating elevated latencies in our email-sending and email-receiving APIs in the US-EAST-1 Region. This includes the control plane APIs as well as calls made to the sending and receiving SMTP endpoints.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 07:02:52 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Elevated email-sending API error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 2:26 PM and 2:55 PM PST in the US-EAST-1 Region, customers experienced elevated error rates sending email to the SES SMTP interface. During that time, a portion of requests failed with a temporary authentication failure. Requests to the SES HTTP interface were unaffected, and all requests accepted successfully by SES have been processed normally. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 15:31:26 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated email-sending API error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 11:38 AM and 12:45 PM PST we experienced elevated error rates for our email-sending API to the SMTP endpoint in the US-EAST-1 Region. This did not affect the SendEmail/SendRawEmail HTTP APIs. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 13:19:34 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Elevated email-sending API error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We've identified root cause and are seeing recovery for elevated error rates to our email-sending API in the US-EAST-1 Region for the SMTP endpoint. HTTP endpoints continue to operate normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 13:00:15 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Elevated email-sending API error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are currently investigating elevated error rates for our email-sending API in the US-EAST-1 Region for the SMTP endpoint only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 12:29:53 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated email-sending API error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 2:35 AM PDT and 7:30 AM PDT we experienced elevated error rates and latencies across our APIs in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 08:15:19 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] SMS Delivery Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 5:14 AM and 11:38 AM PST, we experienced increased delivery latency while delivering SMS messages using US toll-free numbers. Also starting at 5:14 AM, SMS message delivery receipts were delayed, which created a backlog of undelivered delivery receipts. We are continuing to work with our downstream partners to clear this backlog. Receipts for new SMS deliveries will also be delayed until this backlog clears. The issues have been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 14:44:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] SMS Delivery Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm that the delivery of SMS messages for US toll free numbers has recovered. However, we continue to see issues with delivery receipts being delayed and are working with our downstream partners to resolve the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:38:02 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] SMS Delivery Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are seeing early signs of recovery, and continue to work with our downstream partners to fully resolve the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:12:26 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] SMS Delivery Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm that long codes are not impacted, only US toll-free numbers are impacted.  We continue to work with our partners to fully resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:00:01 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] SMS Delivery Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased error rates and delivery latency for a subset of SNS and Pinpoint customers delivering SMS messages via US toll-free numbers and some long codes. We are working with our partners to resolve this issue, and will continue to provide updates until the issue is fully resolved.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 10:59:17 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased SNS Message Delivery Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Recently, we experienced increased SNS message delivery times in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally. We are continuing to process pending message deliveries for a small number of customers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 11:42:55 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased SNS Message Delivery Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to observe significant recovery for SNS message delivery times in the US-EAST-1 Region. All notifications continue to be delivered as we to work towards full recovery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 11:14:36 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased SNS Message Delivery Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have observed significant recovery for SNS message delivery times in the US-EAST-1 Region. All notifications continue to be delivered as we work towards full recovery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 10:17:33 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased SNS Message Delivery Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified the cause of increased delivery times for SNS messages and are working towards recovery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 09:34:29 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased SNS Message Delivery Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased delivery times for SNS messages in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 08:28:18 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates for SMS Delivery</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 9:10 AM and 2:04 PM PDT, we experienced elevated error rates and latencies when delivering SMS messages in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 14:47:51 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates for SMS Delivery</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified the root cause of increased error rates and latencies when delivering SMS messages in the US-EAST-1 Region and are working towards resolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 14:33:24 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates for SMS Delivery</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating elevated error rates and latencies when delivering SMS messages in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 13:52:14 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 2:35 AM and 7:14 AM PDT, Amazon SNS experienced elevated API error rates for all API calls including publish, subscribe, and topic-related APIs. We identified the root cause, the error has been corrected, and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 08:18:09 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are continuing to see recovery on API error rates for all APIs including publish, subscribe and topic-related APIs. We continue to work on restoring full service functionality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 07:57:04 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have completed the mitigation to accelerate processing of the mappings between S3 API request metadata and storage. The backlog has been fully processed and S3 API errors and latencies have returned to normal levels. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 19:51:24 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to process the backlog of mappings between request metadata and data storage in the sub-system affected by the increased load. We have implemented two parallel mitigations to improve the speed of processing. Both mitigations are in process of deployment. Once the backlog is resolved, we expect that the error rate will fully recover. The vast majority of requests to S3 APIs continue to operate normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 18:58:58 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to see a gradual improvement in error rates as we process the backlog of mappings between request metadata and data storage in the sub-system affected by the increased load. We are currently working on mitigations to speed up the processing of the backlog during this event. Once the backlog is resolved, we expect that the error rate will fully recover. The vast majority of requests to S3 APIs continue to operate normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 17:53:09 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are starting to see some improvement in the 5xx error rates and latencies for S3 API requests, in particular S3 PUT API calls. The issue affected a subsystem that stores routing metadata used by Amazon S3 to map API requests to the storage nodes. A recent update caused increased load within this subsystem, which led to increased error rates and latencies for the S3 APIs. We have now successfully mitigated this increased load within this subsystem and are seeing early signs of recovery. As the sub-system processes the backlog of requests, S3 API error rates and latencies will continue to improve.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 16:52:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are continuing to see increased 5xx error rates and latencies for S3 API requests, in particular S3 PUT API calls. We have narrowed down the root cause to a specific sub-system within S3 and continue to make progress in mitigating the impact to this service but have not yet seen significant improvement. S3 API error rates and latencies have stayed a consistent low level with the vast majority of request retries succeeding. While the vast majority of requests are being processed within the normal latency levels, request tail latencies are exceeding 1 second in some cases. In some applications, increasing client timeouts may also help to mitigate the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 16:09:23 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified the S3 subsystem responsible for increased 5xx error rates for the S3 PUT APIs, and are working to isolate the root cause within this subsystem. Customers may also be experiencing increased latency when performing PUT operations. During this time, we recommend customers retry any failed requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 14:48:42 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased 5xx error rates and latencies for requests to the Amazon S3 APIs in the US-EAST-1 Region. Where possible, we recommend that requests that fail with a 5xx error be retried.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 13:58:27 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates for Bucket Operations</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 7:54 AM and 9:18 AM PDT, S3 customers saw elevated errors and latency for a subset of API requests to create and manage Amazon S3 buckets. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 09:30:32 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates for Bucket Operations</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified the cause of the increased error rates for customers creating and managing Amazon S3 buckets and are working towards resolution. Only a small subset of requests are affected and retries are working.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 09:19:05 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED]  Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 9:18 AM and 10:18 AM PDT we experienced slightly increased GET and PUT error rates for Amazon S3 requests in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 10:42:21 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message:  Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified the cause of the increased error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region and are working towards resolution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 10:32:51 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message:  Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates for Amazon S3 GET and PUT requests in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 10:03:21 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated error rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 2:35 AM and 2:39 AM PDT, we experienced elevated error rates for requests in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 03:32:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates for requests to Amazon S3</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have resolved the issue causing increased error rates and timeouts for requests made via Amazon VPC Endpoints to Amazon S3 in the US-EAST-1 Region. Traffic to Amazon S3 via the public endpoints was not affected by this issue. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 09:52:09 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Error Rates for requests to Amazon S3</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm that the elevated rate of errors in Amazon S3 are for requests made to the VPC Endpoint. The Amazon S3 regional endpoint for the US-EAST-1 Region is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 09:10:46 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have resolved the issue causing increased error rates displaying Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) in the VPC Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. This issue only affected the new experience of the VPC Management Console. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 15:10:49 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates displaying Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) in the VPC Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. This issue only affects the new VPC Management Console experience, so switching back to the previous VPC Management Console experience (top left toggle switch) will resolve the issue. The VPC Command Line Tools and APIs are not affected by this issue. We are working to resolve the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 14:54:39 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] VPC Endpoints Error Rates and Timeouts</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 5:57 AM and 7:02 AM PDT and between 8:07 AM and 9:12 AM PDT, we experienced intermittent periods of increased error rates and timeouts for requests made via Amazon VPC Endpoints to Amazon S3 and Amazon DynamoDB in the US-EAST-1 Region. Traffic to Amazon S3 and Amazon DynamoDB via the public endpoints, and all other Amazon VPC functionality was not affected by this issue. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 09:50:24 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: VPC Endpoints Error Rates and Timeouts</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates and timeouts for requests made via Amazon VPC Endpoints to Amazon S3 or Amazon DynamoDB in the US-EAST-1 Region. We are working on resolving the issue, and while the initial impact has been mitigated, we continue to experience periods of increased error rates and timeouts via Amazon VPC Endpoints. Traffic to Amazon S3 and Amazon DynamoDB via the public endpoints is not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 09:02:15 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased VPC endpoint error rates for S3</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 2:26 PM and 2:55 PM PST we experienced increased error rates accessing VPC endpoints for S3 in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 15:40:17 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Network connectivity to new instances</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 7:58AM - 9:57AM PDT, new instances launched into Virtual Private Cloud in the US-EAST-1 region were not reachable via Internet or VPN connectivity. Instance to instance connectivity within a VPC was not impacted. The service is now operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 10:23:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Network connectivity to new instances</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm that beginning at 7:58AM PDT, new instances launched into Virtual Private Cloud in the US-EAST-1 region are not reachable via Internet or VPN connectivity. We are actively investigating the root cause and will provide updates when additional details are known. Instance to instance connectivity within a VPC is not impacted, and Internet/VPN connectivity for instances launched before 7:58AM PDT is not impacted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 09:19:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Network connectivity to new instances</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating network connectivity errors for newly-launched instances in Virtual Private Cloud in the US-EAST-1 region.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 08:53:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated create and delete times</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 11:10 AM PST and 5:20 PM PST, VPN connections in the US-EAST-1 Region experienced elevated creation and deletion times. This issue has been repaired and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 17:32:09 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Elevated create and delete times</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to make steady progress in resolving the issue causing elevated creation and deletion times for VPN connections in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 15:48:20 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Elevated create and delete times</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>VPN connections in the US-EAST-1 Region continue to experience elevated creation and deletion times.   We have identified the cause of the issue and are working to resolve it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 14:37:11 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Elevated create and delete times</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm elevated creation and deletion times for VPN connections in the US-EAST-1 Region. We are working to resolve the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 13:34:26 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Elevated create and delete times</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating elevated creation and deletion times for VPN connections in the US- EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 13:15:07 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 3:13 PM and 4:34 PM PDT VPC experienced elevated API latencies and error rates in the US-EAST-1 region. The issue has been resolved and the service is currently operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 16:50:55 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increase API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are currently investigating elevated API error rates for Virtual Private Cloud in the US-East-1 region.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 16:25:27 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 11:28 AM and 4:05 PM PDT we experienced increased API error rates and delayed group scaling in the US-EAST-1 Region. Connectivity to existing EC2 Instances was not affected. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 16:07:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified the root cause of the increased API error rates and delayed group scaling in the US-EAST-1 Region. We are beginning to see recovery and continue to work toward full resolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 15:45:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are experiencing increased API error rates and delayed group scaling in the US-EAST-1 Region. Connectivity to existing EC2 Instances is not affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 14:02:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 5:05 PM and 5:26 PM PDT we experienced increased error rates for API calls in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 17:33:03 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates for API calls in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 17:22:22 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 5:42 PM and 7:04 PM PDT, we experienced increased API error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:40:14 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified the root cause of the elevated API error rates and can confirm that most customers have recovered. We are continuing to work towards full resolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:24:24 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are continuing to investigate increased API error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 18:26:54 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased API error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 18:06:54 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 9:42 AM and 10:30 AM PDT we experienced increased error rates for API calls in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 10:36:16 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates for all APIs calls in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 10:07:25 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Auto Scaling API errors</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 8:43 AM and 9:26 AM PDT we experienced increased error rates for API calls in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 09:41:18 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Auto Scaling API errors</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates for all API calls in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 09:07:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 12:01 PM and 1:03 PM PST, we experienced increased API faults and instance launch latencies in the US-EAST-1 Region. Existing instances were not impacted during the event. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 13:14:42 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates for API calls in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 12:33:52 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 11:45 AM and 7:42 PM PDT, customers experienced increased ACM API errors and latency in the US-EAST-1 Region that impacted the ability to issue new certificates, import certificates and retrieve information about certificates from ACM. Existing certificates that were already vended to services such as CloudFront and ELB continued to operate and were unaffected. This issue also impacted provisioning and scaling workflows for services that depend on ACM for certificate management needs, such as CloudFront and ELB, as well as CloudFormation operations that involve mutating ACM certificates. This issue was caused by a previously unknown limit in an ACM storage subsystem. We have identified the limit issue and have mitigated it.  The issue has been fully resolved and all ACM API requests are being answered normally.  During this time, all existing resources that had a configured ACM certificate (such as ELB load balancers and CloudFront distributions) continued to operate normally, and were not impaired by this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 19:46:38 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are seeing recovery for customers and throttling has been removed from most APIs.  We have unblocked RequestCertificate for most use cases and are working to have the final changes in-place shortly. We will update as we make progress towards full recovery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 19:05:28 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are seeing recovery for customers and throttling has been removed from most APIs.  We are working through the final changes to unblock the following APIs: RequestCertificate, ListCertificates, and ImportCertificate and expect to have those final changes in-place shortly. We will update as we make progress towards full recovery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 17:47:14 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service disruption: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are starting to see some ACM API calls succeed for CloudFront and ELB and we are starting to propagate changes for CloudFront distributions to our edge locations.  Customer facing APIs are still throttled.  ACM is continuing to make progress towards recovery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 16:49:50 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to work toward mitigating the increased latencies and error rates affecting the ACM APIs. Until this point, some requests and retries have been succeeding. At this time, we are temporarily not accepting additional API requests, in order to help accelerate mitigation and recovery. Once we begin accepting new API requests, requests will be throttled. We will continue to provide updates as we progress.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 15:33:52 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified some workloads on the affected subsystem of the ACM API that may be causing the increase in API errors and latency, and we are reviewing and testing procedures to mitigate their impact.  We do not have an ETA at this time.  This issue does affect services like CloudFront and ElasticSearch that rely on ACM for their certificate needs. It would also impact CloudFormation workflows that either directly or indirectly need to manipulate ACM certificates.

All workflows that depend on ACM certificates that are already created are not impacted by this event, and continue to operate normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 14:56:04 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are continuing to drive to root cause and work toward mitigating the affected subsystem responsible for the increase in API Errors and Latencies for the ACM APIs. Other AWS Services (such as ClientVPN) who attempt to create or associate new certificates may also be impacted by this issue. Existing resources remain unaffected by this issue and continue to operate normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 14:13:09 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to work toward mitigating the affected subsystem responsible for the increase in API Errors and Latencies for the ACM APIs. Other AWS Services (such as ClientVPN) who attempt to create or associate new certificates may also be impacted by this issue. Existing resources remain unaffected by this issue and continue to operate normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 13:14:48 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased API latency and increased API error rates for the ACM APIs in the US-EAST-1 Region. During this time, you may be unable to Request new certificates, and may also observe errors when attempting to List and/or nodify existing certificates. This issue impacts both the AWS Management Console, and the ACM APIs. Additionally, you may also receive API errors when attempting to associate new resources. Existing associated resources are unaffected, and continue to operate as normal. We have identified the root cause of the issue and are working toward mitigation and resolution. We will provide further updates as we have more information to share.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 12:36:19 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latency</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased API latency and error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 12:12:50 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED]  Certificate Issuance Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 12:30 PM and 3:50 PM PST, we experienced delays in issuance of new certificates globally. Existing certificates were unaffected. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 16:34:31 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED]  Certificate Issuance Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating delays in certificate issuance globally. This does not impact existing certificates. Other dependent services utilizing Certificate Manager may be affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 16:00:36 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Certificate Issuance Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 3:05 PM and 6:11 PM PST we experienced increased delays in validation and issuance for DNS validated domains in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally. Certificates waiting for DNS validation which have proper CNAME entries in DNS will validate within the next 3 hours.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 18:20:16 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Certificate Issuance Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to work towards mitigating the increased delays in validation and issuance for DNS validated domains in the US-EAST-1 Region. Certificates that are DNS validated can be requested but will be delayed in issuance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:58:27 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Certificate Issuance Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified the cause of the increased delays in validation and issuance for DNS validated domains in the US-EAST-1 Region and are working to mitigate the issue. Certificates can be requested but will be delayed in issuance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:28:56 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 9:14 AM and 9:52 AM PST we experienced increased error rates accessing the CloudFormation Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. CloudFormation APIs were unaffected by this issue and were still able to be accessed via the CLI or SDK during this event. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 10:40:34 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are beginning to observe recovery for the increased error rates accessing the CloudFormation Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. CloudFormation APIs continue to be unaffected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 10:18:03 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased error rates accessing the CloudFormation Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. CloudFormation APIs are unaffected by this issue and can still be accessed via the CLI or SDK.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 09:51:22 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates accessing the CloudFormation Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 09:39:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Stack Create, Delete and Update Times</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 2:03 AM and 4:03 AM PST we experienced increased latencies for stack creation and deletion in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 04:16:16 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Stack Create, Delete and Update Times</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased latencies for creating and deleting stacks in the US-EAST-1 Region and continue to work towards resolution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 03:56:21 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Stack Create, Delete and Update Times</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased latencies when creating, updating, and deleting AWS CloudFormation stacks in the US-EAST-1 Region and are actively working to resolve the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 03:12:17 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated Stack Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 5:50 AM and 10:50 AM PDT, AWS CloudFormation experienced increased latencies when creating, updating, and deleting AWS CloudFormation stacks in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 11:32:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 8:35 PM and 9:32 PM PDT we experienced increased API error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 21:51:43 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Elevated API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased API error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 21:13:31 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 12:35 PM and 6:20 PM PST we experienced increased latencies for stack creation, deletion, and updates in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 18:35:36 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to unblock the remaining stacks that are pending their update or delete operations in the US-EAST-1 Region. CloudFormation operations for new stacks are working normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 17:31:43 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>New stack operations are progressing successfully and we are in the process of unblocking pending update and delete operations for existing stacks in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 15:49:07 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased error rates and latencies for creating and deleting stacks in the US-EAST-1 Region and continue to work towards resolution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 14:32:40 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates latencies for stack creation, deletion, and updates in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 13:30:57 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 9:37 AM and 8:10 PM PST we experienced issues in delivering CloudTrail log files to destinations in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally. Some customers may see delays in delivering log files from the impacted period of time as CloudTrail works through the backlog.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 20:14:52 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm delivery latency improvements and have started backfilling CloudTrail log files in the US-EAST-1 Region. We continue to monitor latency until fully recovered.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 17:08:22 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm elevated latencies in delivering CloudTrail log files in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 12:10:32 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated event delivery latencies in US-EAST-1</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 2:30 AM and 8:40 AM PDT, CloudTrail experienced delays in processing events in the US-EAST-1 Region. We have resolved the issue. Delayed events are in the process of backfilling. The service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 08:47:39 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: Elevated event delivery latencies in US-EAST-1</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm significant latencies of event delivery and increased error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region. We are actively working to resolve the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 05:47:36 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Elevated event delivery latencies in US-EAST-1</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating delays in delivering CloudTrail events in the US-EAST-1 Region to some users' S3 buckets.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 03:31:31 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Event Delivery Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 12:10 AM and 3:50 AM PDT, we experienced delays in delivering CloudTrail events in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 03:57:38 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: Event Delivery Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are experiencing significant delays in delivering CloudTrail events in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 03:10:41 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Event Delivery Delays</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating delays in delivering CloudTrail events in the US-EAST-1 Region to some S3 buckets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 02:30:37 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] CloudTrail Events Delivery delays to S3</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 10:12 PM on 7/30 and 12:35 AM PDT on 7/31, AWS CloudTrail experienced delays in delivering events in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 00:57:05 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: CloudTrail Events Delivery delays to S3</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating delays in delivering CloudTrail events in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 00:01:10 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Latencies and Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 4:14 PM and 4:22 PM PDT the Lambda invoke API experienced increased latencies and error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 17:22:43 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Invoke Errors</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 12:10 PM and 12:58 PM PDT, we experienced increased invoke error rates and invoke times in the US-EAST-1 Region. This issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 13:21:43 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Invoke Errors</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased invoke times and errors in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 13:08:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Invoke Error Rate</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between October 8 10:35 PM and October 9 2:25 AM PDT we experienced increased Lambda invoke error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 03:11:09 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Invoke Error Rate</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified an increase in invoke error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region and are working towards resolution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 02:03:48 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 8:56 AM and 12:15 PM PST, some customers experienced increased error rates and latencies for actions on the AWS Lambda Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. AWS Lambda API calls via the SDK and CLI were unaffected. Between 11:22 AM and 12:40 PM PST, some invocations of scheduled Lambda functions also experienced elevated error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region. Any unprocessed invocations for affected functions have been reprocessed based on the retry policy on the function. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 13:21:45 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are experiencing increased error rates and latencies for actions on the AWS Lambda Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. AWS Lambda API calls via the SDK and CLI remain unaffected. Some invocations of scheduled Lambda function are also experiencing error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region. The root cause of these issues has been identified and we are working towards full resolution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 12:37:10 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between June 22 5:31 PM and June 23 2:32 AM PDT, we experienced increased error rates for APIs and increased latencies in the US-EAST-1 Region related to Lambda's capacity subsystem. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 03:05:55 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased API Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are currently experiencing elevated latencies for some asynchronus invocations in the US-EAST-1 Region and continue to work towards resolution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 01:26:37 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: Increased API Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have restored capacity and are processing Lambda invocations. Latencies for some asynchronous invocations may be temporarily elevated in the US-EAST-1 Region as we work through the backlog of events.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 23:39:22 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: Increased API Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have restored capacity and are processing Lambda invocations. API error rates and latencies remain temporarily elevated in the US-EAST-1 Region as we complete our resolution steps.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 22:25:46 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service disruption: Increased API Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>As we work toward resolution we are temporarily suspending traffic to US-EAST-1 to restore capacity. Previously accepted events will be processed as soon as service is fully restored.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 21:50:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have identified issues in AWS Lambda&amp;#x27;s capacity subsystem related to the increased API error rates and latencies in the US-EAST-1 Region and continue to work toward resolution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 20:48:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating issues in AWS Lambda&amp;#x27;s capacity management subsystem that are causing increased API error rates and latencies in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 19:47:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates and Latencies</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased API error rates and latencies in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 18:30:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 7:32 AM to 4:56 PM PST we experienced increased error rates and latencies for the AWS Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;

We'd like to share more information about the service event on Tuesday December 7th. Additional details are available below. Should you have any questions, please contact AWS Support. &amp;lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/message/12721/"&amp;gt;https://aws.amazon.com/message/12721/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 17:14:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are seeing improvements in the error rates and latencies in the AWS Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. We are continuing to work towards resolution</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 16:25:28 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are experiencing API and console issues in the US-EAST-1 Region.  We have identified root cause and we are actively working towards recovery.  This issue is affecting the global console landing page, which is also hosted in US-EAST-1.  Customers may be able to access region-specific consoles going to https://console.aws.amazon.com/.  So, to access the US-WEST-2 console, try https://us-west-2.console.aws.amazon.com/</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:26:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates for the AWS Management Console.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:22:57 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 10:26 AM and 12:05 PM PST we experienced increased error rates and latencies for the AWS Management Console in the US-EAST-2 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 12:13:52 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are seeing some recovery in error rates and latencies for the AWS Management Console in the US-EAST-2 Region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 11:46:22 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates for the AWS Management Console is the US-EAST-2 Region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 10:55:42 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated Error Rates for AWS Management Console</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 8:10 AM and 8:39 AM PDT we experienced increased error rates and latency for the AWS Management Console. The issue has been resolved and the console is operating normally.  This issue did not affect any AWS service APIs, they were operating correctly during this time.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 08:47:22 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service disruption: [RESOLVED] Elevated Error Rates for AWS Management Console</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased error rates and latencies for the AWS Management Console.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 08:38:36 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated Error Rates for AWS Management Console</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates and latencies for the AWS Management Console.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 08:30:24 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Management Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 2:38 PM and 3:16 PM PDT, we experienced increased errors for AWS Management Console in the EU-SOUTH-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 15:46:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Management Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased errors for AWS Management Console in the EU-SOUTH-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 15:18:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates and Latencies for SAML Based Federation</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 7:46 AM and 11:37 AM PDT, we experienced periods of request timeouts and increased latencies when attempting to sign-in to the AWS Management Console using SAML based federation. We continue to investigate likely root causes and continue to drive to full resolution. The service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 13:21:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates and Latencies for SAML Based Federation</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are seeing signs of recovery for the timeouts and increased latencies when attempting to sign-in to the AWS Management Console using SAML based federation. We continue to work toward full resolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 12:58:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates and Latencies for SAML Based Federation</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm periods of request timeouts and increased latencies when attempting to sign-in to the AWS Management Console using SAML based federation. We have identified the root cause and continue to work toward resolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 12:24:19 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Latencies for SAML Sign-In</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 7:46 AM and 11:37 AM PDT, we experienced periods of request timeouts and increased latencies when attempting to sign-in to the AWS Management Console using SAML based federation. We continue to investigate likely root causes and continue to drive to full resolution. The service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 13:22:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Latencies for SAML Sign-In</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are seeing signs of recovery for the timeouts and increased latencies when attempting to sign-in to the AWS Management Console using SAML based federation. We continue to work toward full resolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 12:58:22 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Latencies for SAML Sign-In</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm periods of request timeouts and increased latencies when attempting to sign-in to the AWS Management Console using SAML based federation. We have identified the root cause and continue to work toward resolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 12:31:15 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Latencies for SAML Sign-In</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating periods of request timeouts and increased latencies when attempting to sign-in to the AWS Management Console using SAML based federation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 11:41:52 PDT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>