<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>AWS Feed</title><link>http://www.foo.bar/test.xml</link><description>AWS Stuff</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 20:15:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 7:32 AM to 4:56 PM PST we experienced increased error rates and latencies for the AWS Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 17:14:09 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are seeing improvements in the error rates and latencies in the AWS Management Console in the US-EAST-1 Region. We are continuing to work towards resolution</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 16:25:28 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are experiencing API and console issues in the US-EAST-1 Region.  We have identified root cause and we are actively working towards recovery.  This issue is affecting the global console landing page, which is also hosted in US-EAST-1.  Customers may be able to access region-specific consoles going to https://console.aws.amazon.com/.  So, to access the US-WEST-2 console, try https://us-west-2.console.aws.amazon.com/</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:26:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates for the AWS Management Console.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:22:57 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 10:26 AM and 12:05 PM PST we experienced increased error rates and latencies for the AWS Management Console in the US-EAST-2 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 12:13:52 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are seeing some recovery in error rates and latencies for the AWS Management Console in the US-EAST-2 Region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 11:46:22 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates for the AWS Management Console is the US-EAST-2 Region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 10:55:42 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Elevated Error Rates for AWS Management Console</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 8:10 AM and 8:39 AM PDT we experienced increased error rates and latency for the AWS Management Console. The issue has been resolved and the console is operating normally.  This issue did not affect any AWS service APIs, they were operating correctly during this time.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 08:47:22 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service disruption: [RESOLVED] Elevated Error Rates for AWS Management Console</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm increased error rates and latencies for the AWS Management Console.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 08:38:36 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Elevated Error Rates for AWS Management Console</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates and latencies for the AWS Management Console.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 08:30:24 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Management Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 2:38 PM and 3:16 PM PDT, we experienced increased errors for AWS Management Console in the EU-SOUTH-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 15:46:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Management Console Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased errors for AWS Management Console in the EU-SOUTH-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 15:18:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates and Latencies for SAML Based Federation</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 7:46 AM and 11:37 AM PDT, we experienced periods of request timeouts and increased latencies when attempting to sign-in to the AWS Management Console using SAML based federation. We continue to investigate likely root causes and continue to drive to full resolution. The service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 13:21:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates and Latencies for SAML Based Federation</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are seeing signs of recovery for the timeouts and increased latencies when attempting to sign-in to the AWS Management Console using SAML based federation. We continue to work toward full resolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 12:58:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates and Latencies for SAML Based Federation</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm periods of request timeouts and increased latencies when attempting to sign-in to the AWS Management Console using SAML based federation. We have identified the root cause and continue to work toward resolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 12:24:19 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 7:32 AM and 3:10 PM PST we experienced increased API error rates in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 15:31:24 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Increased API Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are experiencing elevated error rates for EC2 APIs in the US-EAST-1 region.  We have identified root cause and we are actively working towards recovery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:49:31 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Network Connectivity Issue</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Starting at 6:05 PM PDT some EC2 instances within a single Availability Zone experienced a loss of power. Other instances within the affected Availability Zone experienced connectivity issues and some EBS volumes experienced degraded performance. The root cause of the event was a loss of power to a single line-up within the affected Availability Zone. Power was restored to the affected line-up at 7:20 PM PDT and at 7:35 PM PDT, the affected EC2 instances and EBS volumes had recovered. The issue has been resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 19:47:21 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Network Connectivity Issue</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We have restored power to the affected line-up and are seeing recovery for the majority of the affected EC2 instances and EBS volumes. We continue to work on the remaining EC2 instances and EBS volumes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 19:34:02 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Network Connectivity Issue</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to work to mitigate the issue affecting connectivity to some instances in a single Availability Zone (USE1-AZ4) in the US-EAST-1 Region. The root cause is a loss of power to a small number of EC2 instances and some networking devices within the affected Availability Zone. A small number of EC2 instances are also experiencing network connectivity issue as a result of the loss of power to the affected networking devices. We are working to restore power to the affected instances. If you are able to launch new EC2 instances, all APIs are operating normally with in the affected Availability Zone. We do not expect the issue to affect any other power line-ups within the affected Availability Zone or other Availability Zones within the Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 19:13:37 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Network Connectivity Issue</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating network connectivity for some instances within a single Availability Zone (USE1-AZ4) in the US-EAST-1 Region. We have identified the root cause and are working to restore connectivity for the affected instances. Some EBS volumes are also experiencing degraded performance due to this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 18:46:19 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Degraded EBS Volume Performance</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Starting at 6:41 PM PDT on September 26th, we experienced degraded performance for some EBS volumes in a single Availability Zone (USE1-AZ2) in the US-EAST-1 Region. The issue was caused by increased resource contention within the EBS subsystem responsible for coordinating EBS storage hosts. Engineering worked to identify the root cause and resolve the issue within the affected subsystem. At 11:20 PM PDT, after deploying an update to the affected subsystem, IO performance for the affected EBS volumes began to return to normal levels. By 12:05 AM on September 27th, IO performance for the vast majority of affected EBS volumes in the USE1-AZ2 Availability Zone were operating normally. However, starting at 12:12 AM PDT, we saw recovery slow down for a smaller set of affected EBS volumes as well as seeing degraded performance for a small number of additional volumes in the USE1-AZ2 Availability Zone. Engineering investigated the root cause and put in place mitigations to restore performance for the smaller set of remaining affected EBS volumes. These mitigations slowly improved the performance for the remaining smaller set of affected EBS volumes, with full operations restored by 3:45 AM PDT. While almost all of EBS volumes have fully recovered, we continue to work on recovering a remaining small set of EBS volumes. We will communicate the recovery status of these volumes via the Personal Health Dashboard. While the majority of affected services have fully recovered, we continue to recover some services, including RDS databases and Elasticache clusters. We will also communicate the recovery status of these services via the Personal Health Dashboard. The issue has been fully resolved and the service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 04:21:06 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Degraded EBS Volume Performance</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We had restored performance for the vast majority of affected EBS volumes within the affected Availability Zone in the US-EAST-1 Region at 12:05 AM PDT and have been working to restore a remaining smaller set of EBS volumes. EC2 instances affected by this issue have now also recovered and new EC2 instance launches with attached EBS volumes have been succeeding since 1:30 AM PDT. Other services - including Redshift, OpenSearch, and Elasticache - are seeing recovery. Some RDS databases are still experiencing connectivity issues, but we’re working towards full recovery. We are in the process of restoring performance for the remaining small number of EBS volumes and EC2 instances that are still affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 03:36:29 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Degraded EBS Volume Performance</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to apply mitigations to address the degraded performance for the smaller set of remaining EBS volumes affected by this issue. While the vast majority of affected EBS volumes were operating normally by 12:05 AM PDT, we have been working to recover a smaller set of affected volumes since 12:12 AM PDT. We continue to make progress on restoring performance for affected volumes, and expect full recovery to take another 2 hours. In some cases, customers may also be experiencing volume state transition delays, which will resolve when the underlying volume has fully recovered.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 02:26:29 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Degraded EBS Volume Performance</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm that the performance has returned to normal levels for the majority of the affected EBS volumes within the affected Availability Zone (USE1-AZ2). Starting at 12:12 AM PDT, we saw recovery slow down some affected EBS volumes as well as some degraded performance for a small number of additional volumes in the affected Availability Zone. We have investigated the root cause and mitigations are underway to complete the performance recovery of the affected EBS volumes.  We continue to work towards full resolution for all affected EBS volumes. In some cases, customers may be experiencing volume state transition delays, which we expect to clear up once volumes have fully recovered.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 01:15:57 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Degraded EBS Volume Performance</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm that the performance has returned to normal levels for the majority of the affected EBS volumes within the affected Availability Zone (USE1-AZ2). We continue to work towards full recovery for the remaining EBS volumes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:30:27 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Degraded EBS Volume Performance</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We can confirm that the deployed mitigation has worked and we have started to see recovery for some affected EBS volumes within the affected Availability Zone (USE1-AZ2). We are still finishing the deployment of the mitigation, but expect performance of affected EBS volumes in this single Availability Zone to return to normal levels over the next 60 minutes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 23:43:32 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Degraded EBS Volume Performance</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to work to address the increased resource contention within the EBS service subsystem responsible for coordinating EBS storage hosts. We have applied several mitigations, and while we have seen some improvements, we have not yet seen performance for affected volumes return to normal levels. We are currently rolling out another mitigation that we believe addresses the root cause and has shown promising signs in testing. We will know within the next 30-45 minutes as to whether this restores normal operations for current affected volumes. For immediate recovery, we continue to recommend that you fail out of the affected Availability Zone (USE1-AZ2) if you are able to do so.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 23:19:25 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Degraded EBS Volume Performance</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to make progress in determining the root cause of the issue causing degraded performance for some EBS volumes in a single Availability Zone (USE1-AZ2) in the US-EAST-1 Region. We have made several changes to address the increased resource contention within the subsystem responsible for coordinating storage hosts with the EBS service. While these changes have led to some improvement, we have not yet seen full recovery for the affected EBS volumes. We continue to expect full recovery of the affected EBS volumes once the subsystem issue has been addressed. For immediate recovery, we continue to recommend that you fail out of the affected Availability Zone (USE1-AZ2) if you are able to do so.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 22:23:09 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Degraded EBS Volume Performance</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to make progress in determining the root cause of the issue causing degraded performance for some EBS volumes in a single Availability Zone (USE1-AZ2) in the US-EAST-1 Region. A subsystem within the larger EBS service that is responsible for coordinating storage hosts is currently degraded due to increased resource contention. We continue to work to understand the root cause of the elevated resource contention, but are actively working to mitigate the issue. Once mitigated, we expect performance for the affected EBS volumes to return to normal levels. We will continue to provide you with updates on our progress. For immediate recovery, we continue to recommend that you fail out of the affected Availability Zone (USE1-AZ2) if you are able to do so.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 21:47:07 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Service is operating normally: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>Between 7:33 AM and 2:25 PM PST, we experienced increased error rates for the Support Center console and Support API in the US-EAST-1 Region. This resulted in errors in creating support cases and delays in routing cases to Support Engineers. The issue has been resolved and our Support Engineering team is responding to cases. The service is operating normally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 15:13:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Service degradation: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We continue to see increased error rates for the Support Center console and Support API in the US-EAST-1 Region. Support Cases successfully created via the console or the API may not be successfully routed to Support Engineers. We continue to work toward full resolution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 13:55:59 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Informational message: [RESOLVED] Increased Error Rates</title><link>http://status.aws.amazon.com/</link><description>We are investigating increased error rates for the Support Center console and Support API in the US-EAST-1 Region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 09:01:31 PST</pubDate></item></channel></rss>